{
    "Q&A Data": [
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What are Xycuno Oobabooga custom nodes for?",
            "Answer": "Xycuno Oobabooga provides custom nodes for ComfyUI to send requests to an Oobabooga instance to assist in creating prompt texts."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the preferred installation method for Xycuno Oobabooga custom nodes?",
            "Answer": "The preferred installation method is using git submodules for custom nodes."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default behavior for `control_after_generate`?",
            "Answer": "The default behavior for `control_after_generate` is `randomize`."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default host for an Oobabooga API?",
            "Answer": "The default host for an Oobabooga API is `http://127.0.0.1:5000`."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default maximum number of tokens to complete the prompt in the Oobabooga node?",
            "Answer": "The default maximum number of tokens to complete the prompt in the Oobabooga node is `200`."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default prompt in the Oobabooga node?",
            "Answer": "The default prompt in the Oobabooga node is an instruction to describe an image featuring the ComfyUI mascot."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default seed used in the Oobabooga node?",
            "Answer": "The default seed used in the Oobabooga node is `0`."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default temperature setting in the Oobabooga node?",
            "Answer": "The default temperature setting in the Oobabooga node is `1.0`."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the default top_p setting in the Oobabooga node?",
            "Answer": "The default top_p setting in the Oobabooga node is `0.9`."
        },
        {
            "Subject": "Xycuno Oobabooga",
            "Question": "What is the Outputs of the Oobabooga node?",
            "Answer": "The Outputs of the Oobabooga node is the text returned by Oobabooga, not including `prompt`."
        }
    ]
}